Uh God, we are not preaching a God we
have only heard. He's a God we have
encountered and we know that indeed he's
a true and a living God. Hallelujah. And
so today I want to continue uh with
discontented
uh we we looked at this last Sunday. We
looked at it last Sunday and even this
day I still want to build upon the
matter to be discontented. We we realize
that this was one of the characters and
the people that were part of the
audience of David in Adulam. And we say
to be discontented is very simple is
when the potential inside does not match
the manifestation outside. It is when
the potential inside does not match the
manifestation outside. And I won't lie
to you in life um as you grow and
outgrow some stuff you must always audit
the abilities you carry versus the
results that you're manifesting. It is
the will of God that we all live and
maximize our potential. Sometimes
premature death is not dying young.
Premature death many times is not dying
young. Jesus died at 33 but he had
fulfilled the assignment. Premature
death is dying with abilities that were
not maximized. That is premature death.
It is dying with abilities that were not
maximized. And that's why you must
interrogate yourself in God.
It is only God who knows you. So you
must search yourself in God to get to
know who you are. Even your parents,
even us who are here, we have no details
of the man and the woman you ought to
be. You can be born in an ordinary home,
go to an ordinary school, live an
ordinary life, but according to
eternity, you are meant to be an
extraordinary person. Somebody said
champions are ordinary men that are
living an extraordinary life. So nobody
was born as a champion. But there is a
nature that can be nurtured and produces
a supernatural being. As I was in
prayer, I think it was on Friday or
Thursday coming to Friday, the Lord gave
me a vision. You know, I pray for the
church and uh and the Lord just gave me
a vision and I I woke up and I laughed
and the Lord showed me my mother. I I
saw my mother uh and and and I was a
very young boy and I saw my mother and
and it was a vision but something that
has used to happen in my life. I saw my
mother uh with um you know they call how
do
you know?
>> Yeah. You know how do you call it in
English?
How do you call in English now? And I
saw my mother with ut and you know when
our parents were preparing to make a
dairy what they used to do they will
select the there there's a certain maze
that they will pick and if there was a
garden nearby they will throw the seed
in there meaning that it is not
qualified for the meal and so they will
disperse there. Sometimes they will
throw the maze and the beans. And then
after some certain rains and a certain
change of environment, you realize that
the seedling shot up again and began to
grow. And I saw a garden where so many
seeds were thrown because according to
my mother, they were not good enough
because they had some element of rot in
them. And the Lord began to tell ME AS
LONG AS THE POTENTIAL PART is not
affected, that seed has the ability to
mature again. And then I saw life
church. The Lord told ME THAT IS WHERE
SEEDS THAT are not needed in other areas
are being thrown. I said, "My goodness."
So I'm dealing with rejected seeds. And
the Lord TOLD ME JUST CREATE AN
ENVIRONMENT AND YOU'LL BEGIN TO SEE THEM
GERMINATE and begin them to mature. And
so in the school of Adilam, I WANT TO
TELL SOMEBODY, YOU MAY NOT HAVE BEEN OF
VALUE IN ANOTHER man's hand, but I WANT
TO ASSURE YOU, WE ARE HERE for the
misfits. Because all we need to do IS
CREATE AN ENVIRONMENT OF the word,
CREATE AN ENVIRONMENT OF PRAYER, AND THE
SEED THAT WAS REJECTED will begin to
mature again. I'm happy they never
touched your potential. It is called a
cautilidon. You remember biology? H AND
SCIENCE. IT IS CALLED THE COTILIGION,
THE THE GERM IN THE MAZE. AS LONG AS IT
IS NOT AFFECTED, IT has the ability to
sprout. AND GUESS WHAT? THAT REJECTED
MAZE DOES NOT produce rotten seeds.
WHATEVER SHOOTS UP AND WHATEVER COMES
OUT IS NOT ROTTEN. NEVER WRITE A MAN OUT
BECAUSE THERE ARE TWO LEVELS. YOU CAN
EITHER BE BURIED OR PLANTED.
THERE. WHEN THE WHEN THE POTENTIAL IS
AFFECTED, YOU ARE BURIED. YOU CAN NEVER
SPROUT AGAIN. BUT WHEN THE POTENTIAL IS
NOT AFFECTED, JUST KNOW THEY HAVE
PLANTED YOU. LET THEM NOT CONFUSE YOU
ARE SILENCE FOR DEATH. BECAUSE THE
PROCESS OF GERMINATION IS A MYSTERY.
IT'S A MYSTERY. THE BIBLE SAYS A FARMER
SWED SEED AND SLEPT BECAUSE IT TAKES THE
HAND OF GOD ACCORDING TO PSALMS THAT IT
IS THE LORD WHO GIVES POWER FOR
GERMINATION. YOU WILL NEVER KNOW WHAT
MAKES THE GOALON to break the shell and
shoot out as another plant. I want to
DECLARE THIS MORNING, YOU HAVE ENTERED
AN ENVIRONMENT WHERE YOU CANNOT DIE.
WHATEVER THAT IS IN YOU, THOUGH IT MAY
LOOK LIKE IT IS COVERED, WHATEVER THAT
IS IN YOU WILL BEGIN TO SHOOT OUT AGAIN.
ANY CORRUPTION THAT THE DEVIL TRIED TO
PLANT IN YOUR LIFE, I WANT TO ANNOUNCE
YOUR POTENTIAL HAS NOT BEEN AFFECTED AND
YOU ARE GOING TO SPROUT AGAIN
BECAUSE I SAW A LAND FULL OF GREEN GREEN
YOU KNOW YOU KNOW GERMINATING MAZE AND
AND IT WAS GREEN AND THE LORD BEGAN TO
TELL ME IT IS THE MISFITS manifesting
again. I know what I'm talking about
because uh some of the pastors even I
dealt with were rejected. Uh and and we
walked and we walked and we I think I
have a grace for rejects. So it's it's a
good thing. It's a good thing.
Tell your neighbor I think he's talking
about you. Mia, you've just found your
company here. Men grow again. H please
stop that neighbor. Tell that neighbor
it's not yet over because the Lord is
not yet done WITH YOU. HALLELUJAH.
AND SO I SAW IT in the spirit and I was
very I was encouraged. I said Lord what
a grace and I discovered that's why we
need to begin the school of adulam. It
it's good to begin that school. So
discont to be discontented is when the
results externally don't match the
potential inside. Are we together? As
long as the enemy has not touched your
potential. Addictions can be released.
Habits and perversions can be released.
But let it not corrupt your potential
because when you rise these things will
be settled. And we looked at a few
factors. Um we looked at the forces of
delay BECAUSE WHEN MAN IS NOT FULLY
MANIFESTING in his potential, it means
there must be some disadvantages that
are working against that man. AND UNTIL
THAT MAN UNDERSTANDS THAT SOME BARRIERS
and disadvantages are working against
him, then he is disadvantaged even to
deal with whatever that is there. We saw
that you can be a a a problem that one
of the problem is the language of closed
heavens. Closed heavens. And and and
this is what I DISCOVERED. THE HIGHER
YOU RISE in life, the lesser you can
incline into atheism.
THE HIGHER YOU RISE IN LIFE is the
lesser you will incline into edism
because you will COME TO AN
UNDERSTANDING THAT LIFE is spiritual and
there are forces beyond logical
interpretation that tend to govern and
CONTROL LIFE. THE MORE YOU RISE IN LIFE,
THERE ARE LEVELS WHERE THE ENEMY WILL
NEVER touch you. AS LONG AS YOU ARE
WORKING FOR YOUR STOMACH, YOU DON'T NEED
WARFARE. YOU JUST NEED SOME SMALL DEVILS
to keep you busy. an addiction here,
women here, YOU KNOW SOME FEW THINGS.
THE DAY YOU BEGIN TO TOUCH SOCIETIES
THAT NOW YOU ARE A CARRIER AND AN
EMPLOYER OF 100 PEOPLE, the day you
begin to MAKE PROPOSALS THAT IS GOING to
lift men FROM BONDAGE AND OPPRESSION,
THAT IS THE DAY YOU'LL DISCOVER THERE
ARE POWERS THAT HINDER PROGRESS. As long
AS YOU ARE WORKING FOR YOUR BELLY, THE
ENEMY will never disrupt your life. BUT
THE DAY YOU BEGIN TO GO BEYOND SELF AND
BEGIN TO DO THINGS THAT HAVE IMPACT ON
THE SOCIETY AND COMMUNITY, you will know
that they are POWERS BEYOND THE POWERS
YOU KNOW THAT TRY TO CONTROL HUMANITY.
And so we saw the concept of the closed
heavens. THE SECOND THING THAT WE SAW IS
THE CONCEPT OF A SPIRITUAL clock where
people operate with certain timings in
the spirit. uh we also SAW THE CONCEPT
OF DEMONIC BARRIERS OR WHAT WE call a
tethering spirit. It looks like people
cannot go beyond a certain set boundary
and anyone who goes beyond that boundary
they must labor in prayer and break the
barriers. We saw the concept of demonic
WATCHMEN PEOPLE THAT STAND AT THE GATES
OF OUR ADVANCEMENT and they tend to
control what comes in and what goes out.
We saw the concept of warfare because
warfares especially triggered by
witchcraft, SORCERY AND SATANISM THEY
tend to slow down the life of a person.
What we need to understand is that
God is powerful
BUT AGAIN EVERYONE COMES FROM CERTAIN
ECOSYSTEMS that are unique. People that
live in areas that are fully dominated
through witchcraft powers and they live
in a territory that has a living altar.
There are disciplines that they must
develop.
All of us are not the same. WE COME FROM
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS. But I want to
tell you our battles also vary. When you
are dealing with witchcraft, sorcery,
WIZARDHOOD, ALL THAT, THE BACKGROUND
INTENTION
OF THE PEOPLE THAT consult witchcraft,
the main assignment and agenda is
control.
That's what they want TO ACHIEVE. IN
FACT, THE ROOT WORD of the word
witchcraft is the WORD CONTROL.
THAT'S WHY WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE BIBLE,
IT TALKS ABOUT MANY THINGS THAT HAPPEN
UPON A PEOPLE and these are the works of
THE FLESH. ANY MAN that wants to control
YOU WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT, THAT IS
WITCHCRAFT. NOW THE ONLY WAY THAT THEY
CAN DO YOU THEY can do that IS NOW
INVOKE CERTAIN POWERS CERTAIN SPIRITS
THAT CAN OVERPOWER YOU SO THAT THEY CAN
HAVE CONTROL OVER your life control OVER
YOUR MONEY CONTROL OVER YOUR FAMILY
CONTROL OVER YOUR RESOURCES. THAT'S WHY
SOME PEOPLE ARE EXERCISING WITCHCRAFT
BUT THEY ARE NOT PER SE WITCHES. YOU CAN
BE MARRIED TO A CONTROLLING MAN. THAT
MAN IS A WITCH.
HE'S ALREADY EXERCISING WITCHCRAFT.
THAT'S WHAT THAT THE POINT I WANTED to
bring home. YOU CAN BE MARRIED TO A
CONTROLLING WIFE, THAT WIFE IS ALREADY
EXERCISING WHAT? WITCHCRAFT. BECAUSE
ANYONE THAT TRIES TO MANIPULATE YOU
without your CONSENT THROUGH EXTERNAL
POWERS, THAT IS CONTROL. AND SO THERE IS
A LEVEL OF WARFARE WHERE PEOPLE TRY to
use the system of altars to invoke
SPIRITS AND POWERS SO THAT THEY CAN COME
AND CONTROL and manipulate your results.
AND WHEN WE ARE DEALING WITH THE ECONOMY
OF WITCHES, we need to UNDERSTAND THAT
IT IS THEY OPERATE IN TWO DIMENSIONS.
ONE, YOU CAN BE IN A PLACE THAT HAS A
living altar. What is a living altar?
This means you ARE IN A PLACE WHERE
PEOPLE SERVICE THEIR ALTAR PERPETUALLY
SO THAT THEY CAN HAVE AN ADVANTAGE OVER
YOUR LIFE. NUMBER TWO, YOU CAN DEAL WITH
AN ANCIENT ALTAR.
THOSE ARE TWO levels of engagement. SO
THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT ARE DEALING WITH
LIVING ALTARS. THAT MEANS YOUR OPPONENT
IS ALIVE. YOUR OPPONENT IS PERPETUALLY
SACRIFICING ON THEIR ALTAR AND YOUR
OPPONENT HAS AN AGENDA TO BRING you
down. WHEN YOU ARE DEALING WITH A MAN
THAT HAS A LIVING ALTAR, YOUR LIFE
CANNOT AFFORD TO BE A LIFE OF SLUMBER.
YOU MUST ARISE AND AWAKE BECAUSE WHEN
YOU ARE SLEEPING, ARROWS ARE BEING
DEPLOYED. THAT'S WHY OUR PRAYER LIVES
CAN NEVER BE THE SAME BECAUSE I DON'T
KNOW WHERE YOU ARE COMING FROM BECAUSE
IF I'M DEALING WITH A LIVING ALTAR, IT
MEANS MY PRAYER LIFE MUST BE ALIVE. IT
MEANS I MUST COUNTER WHATEVER IS BEING
ANNOUNCED. WHEN PEOPLE go to a witch
altar, what they do, they need THREE
THINGS. NUMBER ONE, THEY NEED A PRIEST.
NUMBER TWO, THEY NEED AN ALTAR. NUMBER
THREE, AN ALTAR AND A SACRIFICE. NUMBER
THREE, THEY need words.
Those are the three things that you can
put them for. NEEDED FOR A MAN TO INVOKE
AN ALTAR AGAINST ANOTHER MAN. ONE, THEY
NEED A PRIEST BECAUSE AN ALTAR WITHOUT A
PRIEST IS A MONUMENT. NUMBER TWO, THEY
NEED A SACRIFICE BECAUSE A AN ALTAR
WITHOUT A SACRIFICE AGAIN IS A MONUMENT.
AND NUMBER THREE, THEY NEED WORDS. They
need a priest. They need an altar. THEY
NEED A SACRIFICE. AND THEY need words.
WHEN YOU STUDY WHAT WE CALL UM SPELLING,
THE WORD SPELLING IN THE IN THE IN THE
IN THE IN THE OCCULTIC WORLD, THE WORD
SPELLING IS WHAT SPONSORS THE WORD
SPELLS. SO YOU'LL HEAR SOMEONE HAS CAST
SPELLS. WHAT ARE THOSE? WHEN SOMEONE IS
CASTING SPELLS AGAINST another person,
WHAT THEY ARE TRYING TO DO, THEY ARE
SPEAKING DOOM UPON THAT PERSON. YOU
CANNOT CAST A SPELL UPON A PERSON
WITHOUT an altar, a sacrifice and a
priestly hood. Are we together up to
there? SO WHAT DO PEOPLE DO? THEY WILL
GO CARRY A SACRIFICE, LOOK FOR a priest
and THEN THE PRIEST WILL SLAUGHTER IT
BECAUSE BLOOD BEARS LIFE the innocence
of the animal. The priest will CARRY IT
AND THEN THEY WILL ASK THE PRIEST WILL
ASK THE PERSON WHAT DO you want ME TO
DO? AND THE PERSON WILL NOW CONSENT AND
SAY I WANT PASTOR T MINISTRY TO DIE. SO
THE PRIEST WILL SAY NOW CONCERNING THAT
I KNOW THE SPIRITS I NEED TO INVOKE THE
SPIRIT OF GOSSIP THE SPIRIT OF MALICE
THE SPIRIT OF DIVISION AND THEN HE WILL
NOW DEMAND A SACRIFICE. AND SO WHEN THE
PERSON SACRIFICES WHAT THE PRIEST WILL
DO HE WILL USE YOUR WORDS. WHAT WERE
your words? I want the MINISTRY TO FALL.
AND HE WILL NOW PLANT THE WORDS ON THE
ALTAR, INVOKE THE SPIRITS. AND THEN THE
SPIRITS WILL CARRY THE WORDS AND BEGIN
TO IMPLEMENT WHAT WAS UTTERED. THE
SPELLS THEY WILL BEGIN TO IMPLEMENT. NOW
IF YOU ARE BORN AGAIN, THE BIBLE SAYS WE
ARE NOT ignorant of the devices of the
enemy. SO IF YOU ARE BORN AGAIN, WHAT
YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND, THE ALTAR OF
JESUS is your altar. YOU DON'T NEED
AGAIN TO GO AND BEGIN ANOTHER ALTAR.
LISTEN, YOU DON'T HAVE TO RAISE ANOTHER
ALTAR. THIS LIFE WE LIVE BY FAITH AND
FAITH ALONE. THERE IS AN ALTAR THAT IS
MORE POWERFUL than any OTHER ALTAR. SO,
YOU NEED to begin TO STUDY THE REALITIES
OF THE ALTAR OF CALVARY. YOU NEED TO
BEGIN TO STUDY THE REALITIES OF THE
SACRIFICE OF YESHUA. YOU NEED TO BEGIN
TO STUDY THE PRIESTLYHOOD THAT YOU ARE
GIVEN BY JESUS. BECAUSE THE BIBLE SAYS
NOW YOU ARE A ROYAL PRIESTHOOD. MEANING
THAT YOU DON'T NEED AN EXTERNAL
PRIESTHOOD TO CONTEND FOR YOU. BY THE
DEATH OF JESUS AND BY YOU COMING TO
JESUS, THERE WAS AN ENTHRONEMENT OF
PRIESTHOOD UPON your life.
In Revelation, the Bible says he has
made us unto a kingdom of kings and who?
And priest. LOOK FOR THAT SCRIPTURE.
THAT IS WHO WE ARE. WE ARE A KINGDOM NOT
OF CIVILIANS KAYA. WE ARE A KINGDOM OF
KINGSAN
OF KINSAN. NOW FORGIVE ME BECAUSE I KNOW
ANYONE THAT IS IN AFRICA OUR BACKGROUND
IS A BACKGROUND OF A A A COMMUNITY
PRIESTLYHOOD. WHEN YOU GET TO THE CUKUYO
COMMUNITY THEY HAVE THE TRIBE THAT
PRODUCES A A COMMUNITY OF PRIESTS.
And so IT LOOKS LIKE IF YOU DON'T COME
FROM THE COMMUNITY OF AO or or THE
PRIESTHOOD THEN YOU CANNOT BE A PRIEST
IN THE KINGDOM OF GOD. THE DAY you
became A BELIEVER YOU ENTERED THE TRIBE
OF PRIESTS. NOT IN THE ORDER OF LEVY.
HUH?
AND HAS MADE US WHO?
Kings and
>> priest to who?
>> TO HIS GOD AND FATHER. SO WE ARE ALL
PRIESTS.
I STUDIED THE ORIGIN OF THE LEVITICAL
PRIESTHOOD. It was aka priesthood.
THE ORIGINAL PATTERN OF God was that
every firstborn,
EVERY FIRSTBORN BORN BORN IN A FAMILY
WAS MEANT TO BE the carrier of the
priestly mantle in that family. That was
in the Old Testament. BUT AS THE
CHILDREN OF ISRAEL LEFT EGYPT, AS THEY
WERE COMING IN THE WILDERNESS, THEY
EXALTED the golden calf. AND THE ANGER
OF THE LORD AROSE. AND THE TRIBE OF LEVY
CARRIED THE ANGER OF GOD AND SLAUGHTERED
THEIR own brothers who bowed to that
God. AND BECAUSE OF THAT ACTION, THE
LORD IDENTIFIED with the tribe of Levy
and said, "Out of Levy, I will establish
a priestlyhood." You have to listen
carefully now. AND AFTER THAT
PRIESTLYHOOD WAS ESTABLISHED, THE LORD
NOW CAME AND PUT IT IN THE LAW AND SAID,
"BECAUSE THE FIRSTBORN
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A PRIEST, ONE SET
APART TO SERVE THE LORD, NOW EVERY
FAMILY MUST REDEEM THE FIRSTBORN." YOU
GET WHERE THE DOCTRINE CAME FROM?
BECAUSE THE FIRSTBORN, SO I AM BORN IN A
FAMILY OF SEVEN MEMBERS AND I'M THE
FIRSTBORN. BY THE VERDICT OF BEING THE
FIRSTBORN, I WAS MEANT TO BE THE PRIEST.
NOW, THAT WAS THE PATTERN OF GOD THAT
THE PRIESTHOOD WAS NOT MEANT TO BE FOUND
IN A CHURCH. THE PRIESTHOOD BEGAN FROM A
FAMILY AND SO THAT FIRSTBORN WAS MEANT
TO BE THE PRIEST. BUT WHEN THEY ENTERED
INTO THE SAI THE THE WILDERNESS OF SIN
and they MESSED UP, THE LORD UPLIFTED
THE COVER. BUT HE STILL PLACED A DEMAND
on the firstborn BECAUSE HE SAID THE
FIRSTBORN BELONGS TO ME. AND SO WHEN A
FIRSTBORN WAS BORN, YOU HAD TO BUY THE
FIRSTBORN FROM GOD.
THAT IS NOW REDEEMING. NOW YOU GO AND
TELL THE LORD, "THIS FIRSTBORN IS YOURS.
BUT BECAUSE THE PRIESTHOOD PATTERN HAS
SHIFTED, I WANT TO BUY THE FIRSTBORN TO
ME." THE WORD REDEEM IS TO BUY BACK.
I'm dealing with A DOCTRINE
PASTOR. WHY DON'T WE REDEEM firstborns
pastor? I'M A FIRSTBORN AND I THINK
LISTEN YOU CAN BE A LASTBORN BUT YOU
CARRY THE MANDATE OF THE FAMILY. WE ARE
NOT OH AH JESUS I WENT TO A CHURCH IN
Tanzania and I was told a woman of God
went there and said you need to redeem
the firstborn and and the man of God was
quite smart and and this is what she
said you we need to REDEEM ALL THE
FIRSTBORNS. YOU NEED TO RAISE A SEAT TO
redeem yourself because oh you are the
first who broke the womb and all the
battles. You're the ONE SETTING THE
PATTERNS AND I TELL YOU the theology was
uh amazing to collect a seat because
there are teachings that we can teach
and collect money because you have a
project now and and she said IF YOU'RE A
FIRSTBORN STAND UP AND PEOPLE stood let
me just have IF YOU'RE A FIRSTBORN STAND
UP JUST stand up all the firstborn stand
up all the firstborn stand up now. No,
look, look, this is money. Oh my god. IF
I SAY EVERY FIRSTBORN, YOU NEED TO
REDEEM YOURSELF WITH WITH 10,000 BECAUSE
10 IS THE NUMBER OF DIVINE COMPLETE.
YOU NEED TO REDEEM YOURSELF.
FIRSTBORNS, you need to redeem yourself.
EVERY FIRSTBORN NEED TO REDEEM YOURSELF
WITH 10,000. EVERY FIRSTBORN, YOU NEED
TO GIVE A SEED OF 10. 10 IS THE NUMBER
OF DIVINE COMPLETION. And then I
realized the number is not enough. AND
THEN I SAY IN YOUR HOME YOU MUST HAVE A
FIRSTBORN. STAND. IF YOU HAVE A
FIRSTBORN, YOU HAVE TO PAY A SEED FOR
YOUR FIRSTBORN IS YOUR BROTHER, YOUR
FATHER, YOUR
FIRSTBORN.
OKAY. Can you sit down now, please?
We will not rob you. LET'S TEACH THE
WORD AS IT OUGHT TO BE. AND SO NOW GOD
GOD DECIDED NOW BECAUSE THE FIRSTBORN
WAS MINE. HE must be redeemed from ME
AND HE'S THE ONE WHO MADE THE PRICE OF
REDEMPTION. BUT THE PRIESTLYHOOD
ASSIGNMENT WAS MEANT FIRST TO BE IN A
FAMILY SETUP. NOW AFTER THE LEVITICAL
PRIESTHOOD ENDED BECAUSE FOR A
PRIESTLHOOD TO END IT MEANS ANOTHER
SUPERIOR PRIESTHOOD MUST COME. NOW JESUS
INTRODUCED THE PRIESTLYHOOD in the order
OF MELKCHISEDC. I AM TRYING TO SAY IF
THERE OUGHT TO BE AN ALTAR THERE OUGHT
TO BE A PRIEST. SO MEANING THAT THERE IS
THE PATTERN OF THE DEMONIC. THEY HAVE A
HUMAN PRIEST AND THEY HAVE A HUMAN ALTAR
AND THEY HAVE A HUMAN SACRIFICE AND THEY
RELEASE SPELLS IN THE PATTERNS OF THE
KINGDOM. YOU ARE ALSO A HUMAN ALTAR. I
MEAN A HUMAN PRIEST ORDAINED FROM GOD.
WHEN DID YOUR ORDINATION HAPPEN? THE DAY
THE HOLY GHOST CAME UPON YOU, THAT WAS
THE DAY OF YOUR ORDINATION. YOU DON'T
NEED OIL UPON YOUR LIFE. THE DAY THE
HOLY GHOST CAME UPON YOU. WHEN DID THE
HOLY GHOST COME UPON YOU? THE DAY YOU
SAID, "LORD JESUS, COME INTO MY LIFE."
THAT WAS THE DAY YOU ARE ORDAINED AS A
KING AND AS A PRIEST. AND I CAN TELL
YOU, WE DIDN'T COME WITH CELEBRATION,
BUT HEAVEN KNEW WE HAVE ORDAINED A
PRIEST.
I I like the way you're looking at me
because you don't believe
you. YOU BELIEVE A PRIEST IS A MAN WITH
SHARPSHOOTERS
WITH A COLLAR
AND SOME SOME GARMENTS, RELIGIOUS
GARMENTS. A PRIEST IS A MAN THAT can do
business in the realm of the spirit. YOU
CAN HAVE THOSE COSTUMES, BUT YOU'RE A
STRANGER THERE. IT IS NOT ABOUT THE
GARMENTS. IT'S ABOUT A STATURE IN THE
SPIRIT. AND SO NOW SO PEOPLE HAVE A
LIVING ALTAR. I BLESS THE LORD BECAUSE
ALSO MY ALTAR is not a DEAD ALTAR. THE
ONE I SUBSCRIBE TO. SO NUMBER ONE YOU
ARE A PRIEST. TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR
NEIGHBOR from today you are a priest.
>> And when you pray God hears TELL THAT
NEIGHBOR NEIGHBOR AND GOD DOES NOT HAVE
FAVOR RIGHTS. HE JUST HAS PROTOCOLS.
PASTOR, I KNOW WHEN YOU PRAY, GOD WILL
HEAR. LISTEN, OUR GOD IS A GOD OF
PROTOCOL. IF YOU LIVE RIGHT, IF YOU
UNDERSTAND THE REVELATION AND PRAY
RIGHT, THE LORD WILL ANSWER YOU.
>> I've even seen people who told me to
pray for them and before I prayed for
them, they got answers. That tells them
it's not my prayer. But have you known
sometimes when you go to the hospital,
they they just measure temperature and
pressure and then they give you water
and panador and then you get healed.
Because there is an assumption when I
met the doctor psychologically I'm now
okay. So some of you after calling us I
can can I be read because I'm on the
altar. SOME OF YOU EVEN THOSE THINGS YOU
TELL US TO PRAY for we forget and we
don't pray for you. YOU EVEN COME AND
GIVE A TESTIMONY PASTOR. REMEMBER WHEN I
SAID YEAH OH MY GOD AND THAT'S WHY WE
ARE VERY QUICK TO SAY GLORY TO JESUS
BECAUSE WE KNOW
I NEVER PRAYED. SO I JUST KNOW IT CAN
ONLY BE YESHUA.
But but there are those we pray when we
REMEMBER
Tell your name.
SO WE HAVE SAID THERE ARE FOUR THINGS.
NUMBER ONE, THERE IS A PRIEST. NUMBER
TWO, there is an altar. Number three,
THERE IS A SACRIFICE. And number four,
there are words. For this demonic ALTAR
TO FUNCTION. NOW FOR US TO RISE AND
COUNTER IT, THERE MUST BE another
priestlyhood.
And our priesthood is given BY JESUS.
THE SECOND THING THERE MUST BE AN ALTAR.
NOW I DON'T HAVE AN ALTAR THAT I can
raise. I KNOW PEOPLE HAVE ASKED PASTOR
BUT THIS MAN RAISED SEVEN GOATS. I
RAISED 10. ACCORDING TO THE REALM OF THE
SPIRIT it is called the law of
consolation. WHAT DOES THE LAW OF
CONSOLATION MEAN? It means THAT YOU HAVE
RAISED A MORE POWERFUL SACRIFICE THAN
WHAT THEY HAVE RAISED. NOW THE PROBLEM
IS WHEN THIS LIVING ALTAR INTENSIFIES ON
THEIR SACRIFICE AND YOUR SACRIFICE IS
LOWER IT MEANS they will OVERPOWER YOU.
AND THAT'S WHY THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
PIONEERED THE SYSTEM of seeds.
YOU GAVE A SEED AND YOU WON. NOW YOU'RE
IN BATTLE AGAIN
BECAUSE THE PEOPLE YOU ARE DEALING WITH,
THEY CAN ALSO UNDERSTAND WHEN THERE IS
AN INTERRUPTION.
SO THEY NOW NEED TO INTENSIFY ON THEIR
ALTAR OR EVEN GO TO A HIGHER PRIESTHOOD
TO ENGAGE. SO WE CAN'T SURVIVE BY SEED
BECAUSE IF MONEY CAN BUY YOUR FREEDOM,
YOU DON'T NEED JESUS. JUST BECOME A
BILLIONAIRE. IF THIS THING WAS FOR THE
RICH, THEN THE POOR WILL NEVER HAVE A
PRIVILEGE. SO WHAT THE LORD JESUS DID,
HE CAME WITH THE FINAL ALTAR AND THE
FINAL SACRIFICE TO DEAL WITH ANY OTHER
ALTAR THAT MEN CAN RAISE, MEN WOULD HAVE
RAISED AND EVEN MEN WILL THINK TO RAISE.
SO THE ALTAR OF CALVARY IS THE HIGHEST
ALTAR AMONG ALL THE ALTARS.
JESUS was not crucified ON A VALLEY. THE
LANGUAGE OF AN ALTAR IS THAT IT'S AN
EXALTED MONUMENT THAT CONNECTS THE
HEAVENS AND THE EARTH. AND JESUS WAS
CRUCIFIED ON THE MOUNTAINS OF GOLGODA.
IT WAS AN ELEVATED AREA BECAUSE AN ALTAR
MUST BE ELEVATED ABOVE THE GROUND
BECAUSE IT IS AN ELEVATED AREA THAT
CONNECTS THE HEAVENS AND THE EARTH. IT
IS AN ELEVATED AREA THAT ACTS AS A
PATHWAY OF TRANSACTION BETWEEN THE REALM
OF MEN AND THE REALM OF THE SPIRIT. THAT
IS AN ALTAR. IT IS AN ELEVATED AREA THAT
CONNECTS THE HEAVEN AND THE EARTH. IT'S
AN ELEVATED AREA THAT ACTS AS A GATE OF
TRANSACTION BETWEEN THE HEAVEN AND THE
EARTH. SO JESUS WAS ELEVATED ON AN
ALTAR. AND ON THAT ALTAR, THE LEVEL OF
THAT ELEVATION, NO MAN CAN RAISE ANOTHER
ALTAR GREATER than what was raised for
Jesus.
>> Can we go further? NOW, IN THE NATURAL,
IN THE NATURAL, WHEN MEN RAISE THEIR
ALTAR, THEY NEED BLOOD. THE DEMAND OF
EVERY ALTAR IS BLOOD. WHY DO THEY NEED
BLOOD? BECAUSE LIFE IS IN THE BLOOD.
LIFE IS IN THE BLOOD. And you need life
for an altar to be a living altar.
That's why when you go to the hospital,
THEY TAKE OUT blood to tell you if
you're healthy. YOU HAVE A HEADACHE, BUT
THEY TAKE YOUR BLOOD. YOU HAVE A STOMACH
ACHE, BUT THEY TAKE YOUR BLOOD. YOU HAVE
A SWOLLEN FEET, THEY TAKE YOUR BLOOD
BECAUSE LIFE IS IN THE BLOOD. THE ONLY
WAY WE CAN KNOW YOUR HEALTH is by TAKING
YOUR BLOOD. NOW, THEY NEED THE BLOOD OF
AN ANIMAL. THEY WILL TAKE CHICKEN, they
will take goat, THEY WILL TAKE COWS. BUT
WHEN THEY ARE SERIOUS WITH THEIR MATTER,
THEY WILL NOW BEGIN TO DEMAND FOR
CHILDREN. MANY OCCULTIC ALTARS DON'T
DEMAND FOR FOR FOR GOATS. THEY BEGIN TO
DEMAND for children and not old men
BECAUSE AN OLD MAN IS A SPENT CARTRIDGE.
A CHILD IS A VIRGIN DESTINY. THAT'S WHY
THEY BEGIN TO ASK FOR CHILDREN BLOOD.
AND ANYTIME THEY ASK YOU FOR YOUR FAMILY
MEMBER, THEY ARE THE ONES TO DETERMINE.
WHY ARE THEY DETERMINING? BECAUSE WHEN A
MAN IS TIED TO A DEMONIC ALTAR, THE ONLY
WAY TO SERVE THE DEVIL IS TO DEHUMANIZE
THE MAN. SO THEY WILL COME FOR WHAT YOU
LOVE. SO if it's ME, THEY WILL
INTERROGATE AND REALIZE ANYTIME MY MOM
CALLS I RUN THAT I CAN LEAVE MY WIFE FOR
MY MOM AND THEN NOW THEY WILL MAKE A
DEMAND AND SAY WE NEED YOUR MOTHER. WHY?
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T SERVE THE DEVIL WITH
DIVIDED ATTENTION. THE DEVIL UNDERSTANDS
THE PATTERN OF UNAX.
THAT LANGUAGE OF UNAX, IT WAS A LANGUAGE
OF A MAN DOES NOT HAVE A FAMILY. HE'S
CASTRATED AND HIS ATTENTION IS to the
throne of THE KING. SO ANYTIME THE DEVIL
WANTS TO PARTNER WITH A MAN, HE WILL
ALWAYS PLACE A DEMAND FOR THAT DIMENSION
OF UNACUD WHEREBY YOUR LOYALTY AND
ATTENTION IS UPON HIS THRONE. THAT'S WHY
YOU WILL BEGIN TO ROB THAT WHICH YOU
LOVE. SO THAT NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU
RISE, YOU CAN BE IN A 10BEDROOM HOUSE
BUT YOUR PARENTS ARE SLEEPING HUNGRY
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T GIVE YOU ANYTHING TO
BE A BLESSING to men. IT IS A
TRANSACTION AND THERE IS A
DEHUMANIZATION.
THAT'S WHY NOW THEY BEGIN BUT NATURALLY
IN OCCULTIC ALTARS THEY WILL DEMAND FOR
THE BLOOD OF CHILDREN BECAUSE OF THE
INNOCENCE THAT
>> PASTOR HOW DO YOU KNOW BY FAITH? YES.
>> Because when he was hanging on that
cross, it was a it was a language of
consolation.
So, and when Jesus died, he died for the
things in the past, for the things
present and the things IN THE FUTURE.
THAT tells me I have assurance now and I
have insurance for tomorrow.
>> What a life. And also, my past is
secured. Allow me to teach you faith
because it comes by hearing. I know this
teaching of altars is a good
money-making scheme. But it is also
something that many have been defra many
many have been crowded and they are now
frustrated because they keep on asking
pastor what haven't I done? What you
have not done is to believe. That's the
only thing you've not done. You've
believed your money can deliver you. You
believe your resources can deliver you.
Allow me to surprise you. When God
delivers a man, that man mother's giving
is natural. What can you withhold when
God delivered you from something money
could not buy? BUT YOU SEE, WE HAVE
PROPAGATED THE GOSPEL AND God as a man
that is a businessman who is doing
business WITH OUR MONEY. THAT IS NOT THE
GOD I SERVE. THE GOD I SERVE DOES NOT
NEED YOUR MONEY. He doesn't NEED YOUR
MONEY. IN FACT, WHEN MEN SERVE GOD WITH
THEIR SUBSTANCE, IT IS thanksgiving and
worship. Because the protocols of
worship demand a sacrifice. BUT GOD DOES
NOT NEED YOUR MONEY TO DIE ON THE CROSS.
THE BIBLE SAYS, "WHILE WE WERE STILL
SINNERS, HE DIED for us. BEFORE THE
FOUNDATIONS OF THE WORLD, THE LAMB HAD
ALREADY BEEN SLAIN. BEFORE YOUR
GRANDMOTHER SLAUGHTERED, THE LORD HAD
ALREADY DEALT WITH THAT SLAUGHTER.
BEFORE THEY ROSE ON AN ALTAR TO DECLARE
WHATEVER THEY WERE DECLARING, THE LORD
HAD already dealt WITH IT. SO PASTOR,
HOW DO I DEAL WITH THE LIVING ALTAR in
my family?
One, you must know the revelation of the
altar of Calvary
that you understand that the blood of
Jesus is higher than the blood of bulls.
Even even if I'm told the Freemasons are
here or Satanist and they killed a man
and gave as a human ritual, it cannot
shake me because I know I know for a
fact when we enter in the realm of the
spirit, the blood of that man will
speak. It has speech. But in the realm
of the spirit, the blood of Jesus has
more speech than that blood. So I need
to invoke the speech of the blood of
Jesus. Our parents had revelation. You
know they used to cover everything with
the blood. MY GOD.
HEAR YOUR MOTHER PRAY.
You know the driver work is over.
And and I TELL YOU MIDNIGHT THERE IS
ALWAYS A WITNESS. We will arrive home.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU COME FROM THE MOUNT
KENYA REGION, WHEN YOUR MOTHER PRAYS AND
SAYS,
"HALLELUJAH." YOU BEGIN TO OH MY
GOODNESS. YOU SENSE
YOU BEGIN TO SENSE AN ANOINTING MOVING.
YOU EVEN FEEL LIKE DRIVING AND ASKING,
"WHERE IS THE DEVIL?" MAMA HAS JUST
DECLARED THE BLOOD OF JESUS. I WANT TO
ASSURE YOU THERE'S A REVELATION THAT
THEY HAD. THEY KNEW THAT THERE IS POWER
IN THE BLOOD OF YESHUA. AND I WANT TO
TELL THE CHURCH TODAY, THE BLOOD HAS NOT
BECOME LESS POWERFUL. EVEN TODAY, THE
BLOOD IS STILL POWERFUL. THE BLOOD IS
STILL SPEAKING CONCERNING OUR AFFAIRS.
BECAUSE THE LORD KNEW STRANGE MEN WILL
ARISE. AUNTIES AND UNCLES, COUSINS AND
RELATIVES, VILLAGERS AND TERRITORIAL
MEN, THEY WILL ARISE. AND HE SAID, "I'M
GOING TO FIX THIS MATTER ONCE AND FOR
ALL FOR MORE THAN 2,000 YEARS. I WILL
SHED MY BLOOD. WHOEVER IDENTIFIES WITH
THAT BLOOD, THEY WILL BEGIN TO WALK IN
VICTORY. I DON'T KNOW WHO IS IN YOUR
FAMILY, BUT ALLOW ME TO TELL YOU, THE
BLOOD OF JESUS SPEAKETH BETTER THINGS
THAN THE BLOOD OF BULLS. IT SPEAKETH
BETTER THINGS THAN THE BLOOD OF THE
OCCULTIC AND THE SATANIST. JUST INVOKE
THE BLOOD. JUST INVOKE THE BLOOD. ARISE
ON YOUR ALTAR. IDENTIFY WITH THE ALTAR
OF CALVARY. ENTER INTO THE PLACE OF
PRAYER AND SAY IN THE NAME OF JESUS I
STAND IN THE MOUNTAINS OF CALVARY. I
IDENTIFY WITH THE DEATH AND THE
RESURRECTION OF YESHUA IN THE NAME OF
JESUS I NOW DEPLOY THE BLOOD OF JESUS.
ANYONE THAT HAS SHED BLOOD CONCERNING MY
LIFE, MY FAMILY, MY CHILDREN. NOW I
ARISE WITH A GREATER BLOOD AND I DECLARE
NOW LET THEIR BLOOD BE NEUTRALIZED. THEY
CANNOT BRING ME DOWN. I COVER MY
CHILDREN. I COVER MY BUSINESS. I COVER
LIFE CHURCH. I COVER MY LIFE. UH THAT IS
HOW YOU ENGAGE BECAUSE THEY WERE
SPEAKING ON THEIR ALTAR. SOMEBODY MUST
ALSO APPLY WORD. THAT WORD WE CALL IT
PRAYER. BEGIN TO DECLARE THE AUTHORITY
FOR MORE THAN 2,000 YEARS. THAT
GRANDMOTHER WHO SLAUGHTERED I DON'T KNOW
THE NAME, BUT I STAND ON THE COVENANT OF
YESHUA. HE THAT WAS, HE THAT IS, AND HE
THAT IS TO COME. MAY HE BEGIN TO FIX MY
PATH. ANYTHING SAID, ANY AGREEMENT, ANY
COVENANT, I NOW IDENTIFY WITH THE
COVENANT OF YESHUA. I AM A CHILD OF GOD.
I AM UNDER THE BLOOD. I AM UNDER THE
COVENANT, THE NEW COVENANT. THAT IS HOW
YOU PRAY. YOU DON'T BEGIN TO SAY,
"PASTOR, CAN I COME WITH A SEED? OH, THE
LORD BECAME YOUR SACRIFICE. CALVARY
BECAME YOUR ALTAR. YOU ARE NOW A
PRIEST." AND THE WORD OF GOD, THE WORD
OF GOD IS THE SPELL YOU RELEASE ON THAT
ALTAR. OH MY GOD. WE DON'T NEED TO FEAR
WITCHES. WE DON'T NEED TO FEAR THEM. WE
CANNOT BE DELAYED. LET THEM WALK NAKED
AROUND OUR BUSINESS. LET THEM DO
WHATEVER THEY NEED TO DO. WHEN YOU STEP
FROM ANOTHER PRIESTLYHOOD, LET THEM KNOW
ANOTHER GOVERNMENT HAS COME. I COME IN
THE NAME OF THE LORD. THE BIBLE SAYS
THAT WE NEED TO CONDEMN. WE NEED TO
CONDEMN EVERY TONGUE RAISED AGAINST US
IN ACCUSATION. YOU CANNOT BE QUIET WHEN
MEN ARE SPELLING MATTERS CONCERNING YOUR
DESTINY. YOU CANNOT BE QUIET WHEN A MAN
IS CURSING YOU ON AN ALTAR. YOU NEED TO
WAKE UP AND BEGIN TO ANNOUNCE, "I AM
BLESSED OF THE LORD. I CAN NEVER BE
CURSED. I LIVE ABOVE THE REALM OF
CURSES. I AM SURROUNDED BY THE FIRE OF
THE HOLY GHOST. I AM ABOVE ONLY. I CAN
NEVER GO DOWN. I AM STRENGTHENED BY THE
HOLY GHOST." YOU NEED TO SPELL THE WORD
OF GOD OVER YOUR LIFE.
HALLELUJAH.
You can have your seats BECAUSE WE ARE
HAVING A GENERATION THAT HAS BEEN
INTIMIDATED by witches.
>> No, we come from a higher order. THE
ONLY WAY TO UNDERSTAND THE POWER you
carry is when some challenges come.
I met a woman, a woman of God, a woman
of prayer. They in the office they
bewitched her. Seven women gathered.
They wanted her out of office in the
county.
And what they did they went to a very
senior witch
and they agreed them the woman will die
as she's coming from Kito
and they they attacked the driver and as
the driver was driving he began to say I
don't know why I just feel like I want
to die. So they had released the spirit
of death and the woman began to pray in
the Holy Ghost. She began to declare
life. The car was swerving but they
never had any accident. They arrived in
Auru. He told the driver, "Can you park
this car here and go? Take him a tattoo
and go." And she drove it. When she
arrived on Monday in the office, one of
the ladies came crying, saying, "We are
sorry.
We were assured on Saturday you'll be
dead." and I don't know what will happen
to us because we were seven of us and we
wanted you dead and the woman revealed
everything.
And the woman looked at them and just
laughed because the problem is when a
demonic arrow backfires
it goes.
DO YOU KNOW WHY THERE ARE PEOPLE PEOPLE
can try to be with you?
Because when a priest releases an arrow,
it is either coming back to the priest.
Pastor Jimmy prayed with a with a with a
woman one day. The woman went to a witch
and they said, "I want my husband back."
And and she was asked, "What do you
want?" She said, "I want my husband back
and I want him in a status that I want
to see him here every day in a way that
I can be seeing him here and not doing
anything but let him sit here and let me
have control." The man activated his
system and then the woman was called and
she was told your husband is in a hotel
Akiluka.
So she called pastor Jimmy and said I
need my husband back.
So the man called and said the arrow I
have released I can't receive it because
that madness will come to me. So give me
another landing ground
because it's already launched. And
that's why you hear people say back to
sender. It's a very Oh my god.
You know, YOU KNOW WE SHOUT THINGS
WITHOUT UNDERSTANDING. WHEN A DEMONIC
DEPLOYMENT HAS BEEN DONE AND IT REALIZES
IT cannot land. Do you know the BIBLE
SAYS A CURSE without a cause is like a
pad. It has no GROUND FOR LANDING. THAT
MEANS IF IT cannot land and it was
instructed, it will either go back to
the witch that sent it or that witch
will now divert it to the one that
instructed for that arrow to BE
RELEASED. THAT'S WHY WHEN YOU RISE AS A
BELIEVER, they will call you a witch.
>> Because the witch will realize I am
dealing with ANOTHER POWER. THAT'S WHY
WE NEED TO PRAY. HALLELUJAH.
>> HALLELUJAH.
DEPRESSION.
THAT is where the POWER IS.
SO I'M NOT AFRAID OF A WITCH.
EVEN IF THEY CAME HERE AND GATHERED, I
WANT TO REMIND THEM, EVEN IF THEY
WATCHING ONLINE BECAUSE YOU NEVER KNOW,
SOME GATHER WITH US. I WANT TO REMIND
THEM, I'M UNDER THE BLOOD OF YESHUA. AND
IF YOU WANT TO TEST THAT BLOOD, OH MY
GOD, WHEN HE WAS DYING ON THE CROSS, HE
GAVE SPEECH TO HIS BLOOD. Because when A
WITCH IS SLAUGHTERING, THEY GIVE SPEECH
TO THEIR BLOOD. WHEN HE WAS DYING ON THE
CROSS, HE NEVER DIED SILENT. HE SAID,
"IT IS FINISHED." WHAT HE WAS MEANING,
THE BATTLE IS OVER. THE ENEMY HAS NO
POWER OVER THE CHURCH. HE'S PERPETUALLY
DEFEATED. AND THAT FINISHED, IT WAS NOT
A ONE-DAY EVENT. IT WAS A PERPETUAL
VICTORY. THAT'S WHY THE BIBLE SAYS WE
ARE MORE THAN CONQUERORS. WE DON'T FIGHT
FOR FOR VICTORY. WE FIGHT FROM THE
COMPLETE WORK OF CALVARY. WE ARE HERE TO
ENFORCE AND ENDORSE THAT WHICH JESUS HAS
ALREADY IMPLEMENTED UPON OUR LIVES. I
WANT TO DECLARE VICTORY OVER YOUR LIFE.
ANY MAN THAT HAS CONTENDED WITH
WITCHCRAFT, ANY MAN THAT HAS CONTENDED
WITH SORCERERS, ANY MAN THAT HAS
CONTENDED WITH OCCULTIC MEN, YOU LIVE IN
A TERRITORY WHERE THEY HAVE DOMINATED. I
SEND YOU IN THE PRIESTHOOD NATURE OF
CHRIST AND I DECLARE BY THE COMPLETE
WORK OF CALVARY. NO ANCIENT ALTAR, NO
CURRENT ALTAR, NO FUTURE ALTAR WILL EVER
ARREST YOUR LIFE, ARREST YOUR CHILDREN,
ARREST YOUR CAREER, ARREST YOUR FUTURE.
WE NEUTRALIZE THE POWER. WE NOW DECLARE
BY THE VERDICT OF YOUR SALVATION. NOW
THAT YOU ARE BORN AGAIN, WE WANT TO
DECLARE, LET THE BLOOD OF YESHUA SPEAK.
LET THE COMPLETE WORK OF CALVARY BECOME
YOUR PLACE OF TRANSACTION. WHATEVER WAS
HELD IN DARKNESS, WE ANNOUNCE NOW BY
THIS REVELATION, LET IT BE RELEASED.
EVERY ARROW RELEASED UPON YOUR LIFE FROM
THE QUARTERS OF DARKNESS, WE SPEAK TO
THE ARROWS, NOW GO BACK TO THE SENDER.
PEOPLE THAT HAVE BEEN STANDING ON THEIR
ALTAR TO C US WITH OUR PHOTOS, WITH THE
PHOTOS OF OUR CHILDREN, WITH THE NAMES
OF OUR BUSINESS. PEOPLE THAT BOUGHT
STUFF FROM US AS A POINT OF CONTACT TO
GO AND KILL OUR BUSINESS. WE STAND ON
THE ALTAR OF CALVARY. WE DECLARE WE
CANNOT BE FINISHED. WE CANNOT CLOSE. WE
CANNOT DIE. HE THAT IS IN US IS GREATER
THAN HE THAT IS IN THE WORLD. WE DECLARE
OUR BUSINESSES CANNOT CLOSE. WE ARE NOT
THE TYPE TO BE FIRED BECAUSE OF A
POLITICAL OVER OF A WITCHCRAFT
CONSPIRACY. MAY THE LORD ARISE. I SAY
MAY THE LORD ARISE THAT HIS ENEMIES MAY
BE SCATTERED.
I SENSE AN ANOINTING.
WE deal with every witchcraft power
because we ARE LIVING IN A DAY WHERE MEN
ARE PURSUING DIFFERENT SPIRITUALITY.
SOMETIMES IT MIGHT MANIFEST AS INFIRMITY
IN YOUR BODY. EVERY INFIRMITY THAT CAME
AS AN ARROW FROM DARKNESS, RECEIVE YOUR
HEALING NOW. LET THE PAIN LEAVE YOUR
BODY AND NEVER TO COME BACK AGAIN. LET
THE PAIN LEAVE YOUR BODY. ANY MAN THE
BIBLE SAYS AND THEY ARE MEN THERE ARE
MEN WHO GATHERED AND THEY VOWED WITH A
VOW THAT THEY WILL NOT EAT UNTIL THEY
KILL PAUL AND THE BIBLE SAYS THERE WAS
INTELLIGENCE THAT WAS DEPLOYED AND THE
LORD DELIVERED PAUL I DON'T KNOW WHO HAS
VOWED WITH A VOW THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO
STAND ON THEIR ALTAR AND THEY SAY I VOW
THAT THIS PERSON IF THEY DON'T GO DOWN
LET IT BE CALLED LET IT BE CREDITED ON
MY NAME WE DON'T CARE WHAT VOW THEY HAVE
MADE BUT TODAY WE WANT TO DECLARE THEIR
VOWS WILL NOT PREVAIL. THEIR VOWS WILL
NOT PREVAIL. EVERY VOW MADE AGAINST YOUR
LIFE WE NULLIFIED. YOU ARE A CHILD OF
GOD. YOU ARE UNDER THE PROMISES OF THE
LIVING GOD. WHATEVER THE LORD HAS
UTTERED ACCORDING TO JOSHUA. THE BIBLE
DECLARES THAT EVERY GOOD WORD UTTERED
UPON ISRAEL, IT CAME TO PASS. I DECLARE
TODAY EVERY WORD ANNOUNCED OVER YOUR
LIFE, EVERY UTTERANCE MADE OVER YOUR
LIFE, EVERY PROMISE, EVERY PROPHECY,
THAT IS THE VOW THAT WILL WORK FOR YOU.
SOMEBODY JUST STAND UP BY SEVENTH PLACE
FOR PRAYER. BEGIN TO CONTEND WITH
MATTERS.
EVERY WITCHCRAFT IN MY FATHER'S HOUSE.
MAY THE LORD ANOINT YOU NOW WITH A GIAN
ANOINTING. YOU WILL NOT BE AFRAID.
WHATEVER YOUR FATHER COULD NOT DESTROY,
RECEIVE THE ANOINTING NOW. WHATEVER YOUR
MOTHER COULD NOT DESTROY, RECEIVE THE
ANOINTING NOW.
WITCHCRAFT POWERS, ALTARS OF DARKNESS,
WE ARISE IN THE NAME OF YESHUA MASHIA.
SOME MARRIAGES ARE UNDER WARFARE BECAUSE
MEN ARE TRYING TO CONTROL YOUR LIFE FROM
A PLACE OF AN ALTAR. WE COME WITH THE
ALT OF YESHUA. WE COME WITH THE ALT OF
YESHUA. WE COME WITH THE ALT OF YESHUA,
THE COMPLETE WORK OF CALVARY. YOU ARE
MORE THAN A CONQUEROR. YOU ARE
VICTORIOUS. YOU HAVE WON THE BATTLE. YOU
HAVE WON THE BATTLE. YOU HAVE WON THE
BATTLE. LET THE YOKE BREAK. LET THE YOKE
BREAK. LET THE POWERS
IN THE NAME OF JESUS.
EVERYBODY LIFT UP YOUR HAND. SAY IN THE
NAME OF JESUS I identify with the
complete work of Calvary. Today I
declare anything
TIED BY POWERS OF SORCERY, WIZARDHOOD
AND WITCHCRAFT, SATANISM AND OCCULTISM
IN MY TERRITORY IN MY LIFE. I DECLARE BY
THE SPEECH OF THE BLOOD I AM FREE. I AM
A VICTOR. I AM RISING IN JESUS NAME.
Somebody celebrate the Lord.
Let's have our seats. My goodness,
something must give way. So whether it's
a living altar, when it's a living
altar, it means you must survive by the
realities of Calvary. When it is a
ancient altar, you just need one
operation to bring it down. As we were
praying, I had the word Gideon mantle
because some of our parents did not have
the revelation we are having. It was
Gideon who dealt with the gods in his
father's house. There can never be
national victory if you have not
conquered household gods. That's the
first area. The first victory in your is
in your family. That's why you must
redefine the history of your family. You
must you must beat the poverty. You must
beat the patterns of marriage. You must
beat everything that has defined your
family so that now we can launch you to
the next level. So that we can launch
you to the level of conquest. Gideon
could not have won a national battle
with an existing God in his father's
house. That's why these matters are very
important. The Lord can make you a
firstborn in the spirit to be the one
managing the spiritual conversations and
affairs of a family. Hallelujah. Once
you have conquered a family altar, you
are now ready for national altars
because the pattern is the same. Gideon
said to his father, "Is Bal is God? Let
him fight for himself." The days for men
fighting for their God is over. Let gods
fight for themselves. And he knew, I am
not the one to deal with Bal. The God
that has sent me is the God that will
deal with Bal. He came from a place of
revelation. And that is what will make
you go. The whole village waited for the
man to die and they realized indeed Bal
is not God. May that be your testimony
in Jesus name. I say may that be your
testimony in Jesus name. Hallelujah.
So that's why we cannot afford to sleep.
Please never confuse the life of your
neighbor to be your life. Some of us we
are the first to get born again in our
homes. Some of us we we have no brothers
and sisters we can call for partnership
in prayer. So I have no backup. I bless
the Lord your father was a deacon.
I bless the Lord your mother right now
is the chair lady of women and all your
aunties are intercessors. You have a you
have an advantage in the spirit. For me
it is me and my God
because I'm the first in my family to
attempt to do what I'm trying to do. So
my prayer life cannot match your prayer
life. When you see me shake my head like
a madman, I am setting a pathway for
generations.
You may not understand me if you don't
know where I'm going. Hallelujah. If you
know you are part of my team, you can't
afford to stay. You know in school there
are people who who are book smart.
Someone will just stay in a class, write
notes and they cram anything. Some of us
we had to read three times. Read the
notes, write short notes and do short
notes of short notes and then before
exam read everything the notes the short
notes and short notes of short notes and
and sometimes when you are doing the
notes the guy the guy that is book SMART
IS SLEEPING. SO YOU CAN'T BE A FOOL AND
THINK THAT YOU are like this guy AND
WHEN THE EXAM COME THE MAN IS GETTING AN
A. YOU must know where you operating
from in the spirit and JUST KNOW MINE MY
PATH IS different but this one path is
also different. There are people even if
they don't pray there are people crying
for them. You I don't know who's praying
for you.
I DON'T KNOW WHO'S PRAYING FOR YOU. SO
SO WE MUST BE SERIOUS. ARE we together?
Now let's look at this other point. I
have a few minutes. Are you learning
something?
>> Yes. So
so so and I tell you when when you begin
to rise you'll understand the language
of altars. Because when you enter some
levels in the marketplace, when you
enter some levels uh even in your
career, you'll now discover that men
don't sit in boardrooms. Men are backed
up by certain forces. That's why I say
majority of the Christians are jokers or
I can put it like this. Maybe the altar
or the churches we attend have not
matured enough to understand the
competition we are facing. And so we are
not raising men that are surviving on
spiritual backup. Majority of our people
are surviving on intellectual backup on
capacity but not stature. Majority of
the people and and that's what I want to
talk about because the next level of
your sustainance will not be because of
academics. After you get your PhD, after
you get all these documents, you'll
discover that when people meet in
boardrooms, it's an assembly of altars.
H.
Now let me ask you today you want to do
business with an Indian.
Indians are not atheist.
Before you do any transaction with an
Indian, they must address their altar.
They must address their altar. Before
you do any transaction with a Muslim,
they must address their altar. We have
backgrounds uh connected to Muslims and
they do a lot of slaughtering. They have
their imams. They have the Malims.
They have people who read their palms.
Sometimes you might enter meeting in a
Muslim and you don't know they they had
to take shower with certain habs
because it's an instruction. They have
people who give them intelligence like
divination.
That's a that's a level of the
prophetic. So a man can go
you you are sleeping and waking up at 4,
not at 4. You're waking up at 10 because
you have a deal at 12. A man on Friday
consulted his gods and he's coming from
a place of intelligence
because that's the language of Islam. He
has a grace of business. You do with
him, you will prosper. And then you
enter into alliances and covenants. And
I'm not here to preach religious hatred
because we won't sell our goods to
Christians only. I'm just here to preach
consciousness of spirituality because we
are so casual with our staff. And that's
why when we get out, we leave battered
and butchered. Those people don't just
sit in boardrooms, they consult widely.
They have their priest that give them
intelligence. And and I know because and
they understand forces of activation. I
met an Indian and he told me I'm happy
when this deal goes through. I'm happy
I'll be able to feed the poor because
for the last 20 years we have been
giving the poor people food on Sunday.
For the last 20 years in Kang it's there
every Sunday they are feeding the poor.
They understand there is a principle
spiritually that God can accept the
offering of Cornelius who is a Roman
soldier. And what is Cornelius giving?
He's giving arms to the poor to a point
that God can interrupt the sleep of an
apostle because he's not just interested
with the arms. He's not interested with
the soul of the man. Some of us don't
even understand the language of arms
giving. They call them philanthropies,
but it is a key for opening of
appetance. When a poor man is blessed,
he doesn't praise the one who gave him
the food. He praises God. Because a poor
man dependency is in God.
Am I speaking to anyone? You realize
whatever church is introducing as arms
is not arms. It is marketing strategies
of church. I don't need to give members
flat to come to church. That is bribe.
But I can identify a needy person.
I've met many rich people and they will
always I met one guy and he told me this
guy pays school fees to more than 30
people and he doesn't shout so we give
flour on camera.
Do you know it is the scripture that
says whatever the right gives the left
should not know. That is not offering
its arms.
It's arms. It means it ought to be so
much from a place of conviction but not
from a place of pride. Sometimes photos
are taken for accountability. I even
told pastor Eugene never take the image
of the person benefiting. It is not it
is not their wish to be there. I wish
you could see us when we were in primary
school shorts with patches. You look
brown
and we were there singing to an MP so
that we can be GIVEN MONEY. NOW IF THEY
TOOK ME A PHOTO THAT WAS AN APOSTLE WHO
HAD DESTINED IN FUTURE BUT BECAUSE OF
CIRCUMSTANCES OF LIFE I WAS THERE.
HALLELUJAH. I'm happy they didn't take a
photo
left.
And I tell you the truth,
Fanta have litter.
So tell your neighbor, neighbor,
>> we need to be serious with our
spirituality.
Are we together? Because
I I know God is going to raise you.
You'll sit on these tables. Some of you
are already sitting there and you
discover that men don't joke with their
patterns. When you go TO DUBAI, WHEN MEN
ARE GOING TO MECCA, they have to go with
white skirts and some stuff and that's
how they enter airport. They are not
afraid. Sometimes I love their
testimonies public
BUT BUT PERSONALLY I FEEL LIKE THIS IS A
RADICAL STEP of saying you know I'm a
believer and there are certain values
that I uphold to. SO THE CHALLENGE HERE
HAS ALWAYS been the second thing and I'm
going to take a FEW MINUTES. THE SECOND
THING THAT HAS THAT THAT THAT that
causes men not to expand their to fully
manifest their potential is the battle
of capacity and stature. The battle of
capacity and stature.
The battle of capacity and stature.
Everyone is humble as an intern.
Wait until the day they will be made the
manager of the company. As an intern,
you obey all the laws. The day you
become a project manager, you now
discover their HR policies and you have
rights. And there's no problem with
that. MANY PEOPLE ARE VERY COMMITTED to
God when things are not working. But
wait until a door opens and we no longer
see them in church.
This has happened even in government.
YOU FIND PEOPLE THAT ARE VERY
APPROACHABLE AND PEOPLE THAT ARE VERY
GOD-FEARING TODAY WHEN THEY OPEN THEIR
MOUTHS ON POLITICAL GROUNDS. You wonder
who pastored this one.
MAJORITY OF THE PEOPLE I KNOW BECAUSE
KENYA WAS WELL EVANGELIZED.
MAJORITY OF THE PEOPLE in our land they
know God.
BUT IMMEDIATELY AFTER SOME DOORS WERE
OPENED they now left God because the two
must grow hand in hand. Stature and
capacity.
Capacity.
Capacity is the ability to handle things
through skills. That's capacity is the
ability to handle things through skills.
That's capacity.
The ability to handle things, problems,
issues through skills.
AND EVEN THE BIBLE IS VERY CLEAR ABOUT
SKILLFUL PEOPLE.
It's clear. Show me a man skillful, he
will stand before great men, not mere
men. Skills are very important. Skills
are very important. I believe it's in
the book of Proverbs. Is it Proverbs
18:16 or 22:29?
SHOW ME A MAN THAT IS SKILLFUL.
He will begin to attract an audience
because in the marketplace, men employ
skills.
Men employ skills. Look for that
scripture. Proverbs 18:16 and Proverb
22:29.
MARKETPLACE. THEY DON'T EMPLOY
ANOINTINGS.
They look at your CV.
Look for the other one. 22 29
22 29.
Everybody read. Do you see a man who
excels in his? It's a question. This
word excel. This is a skillful man. A
SKILLFUL MAN. AND ONE OF THE
DISADVANTAGES OF CHURCH is the spirit of
mediocrity.
THE SPIRIT OF MEDIOCRITY.
THERE ARE PLACES WHERE FAITH IS NOT
NEEDED is your skills.
And skills are acquired. They are not
prayed for.
SKILLS ARE EXERCISED and sharpened.
It is work skills are acquired.
THE REASON WHY INDIA
HAS THE BEST HOSPITALS.
One of the girls went there for her
internship AND SHE REALIZED THE DOCTORS
study for 18 to 22 hours.
And if YOU ARE A DOCTOR THAT DEALS WITH
KIDNEYS, that's your work. THERE IS
NOTHING ELSE YOU STUDY. IT'S the kidney.
18 to 22 hours reading about kidney.
NOW THESE DOCTORS ARE NOT BORN AGAIN BUT
BELIEVERS DO HARAM in church
to take a pastor
to India
because we have raised anointed doctors
but not skillful.
but it's because I love you. Somebody
say skills.
>> Skills are acquired. You must acquire
them. Nobody was born WITH SKILLS.
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE GO TO SCHOOL. THAT'S
WHY PEOPLE GO to school to acquire
skills.
and skills are sharpened,
we can all go to the same driving
school.
BUT IF I BEGIN TO DRIVE AND CONTINUE
DRIVING AFTER ONE YEAR, THE ONE WHO went
to a DRIVING SCHOOL AND GOT A DRIVING
license will not have the skills that I
HAVE BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN EXERCISING
whatever I was learning. THERE ARE
PEOPLE WHO ACQUIRED skills but they
don't exercise them. SO WHEN IT COMES TO
THE PLACE OF COMPETENCE, THEY HAVE
NOTHING to offer because THEY DON'T
EXERCISE. AND SOMETIMES GOD WILL PUT YOU
IN STRANGE PLACES to sharpen your
skills.
SO YOU ARE EMPLOYED AS AN INTERN AND
EVERYONE IS GIVING YOU THEIR WORK AND
YOU ARE MAD BUT GOD IS SAYING I'M
sharpening your skills because of where
YOU'RE GOING. THAT'S WHY ATTITUDE
BECOMES A VERY important thing. I read
the story of the sentime CEO James Moria
AND AND JAMES MORIA WAS a he was a
STOREKEEPER BOOKKEEPER AND WHEN HE WAS
BORED HE USED TO READ THE COMPANY BOOKS.
SO AS HE WAS WORKING IN THE CORRIDOR HE
DISCOVERED THE COMPANY wants to hire a
certain person in a certain managerial
PLACE AND HE APPLIED. HE WAS NOT THE
QUALIFIED BUT BECAUSE HE KNEW THE BOOKS
of the company. HE HAD READ EVERY BOOK.
HE UNDERSTOOD process procedure. WHEN
THE EXTERNAL PEOPLE CAME, THEY DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT HE KNEW. That's how he got the
job. Today is one of the highest paid
CEOs from a very minimal position where
he was exposed and began to sharpen WHAT
HE HAD. WHERE YOU BEGIN IN LIFE IS not
the issue. The issue is what are you
doing with what you have?
WE LIVE IN A SEASON OF MULTI-TALENTED
AND MULTIACETED MEN. THAT IS our curse.
You must be a master of something.
YOU CANNOT BE A JACK OF ALL TRADES.
Some of you, we know you.
in your next I can also facilitate human
kidney. Listen,
listen. You must be a master of
something. THE WORLD is not looking for
jacks. Is looking for mastery. That's
why you must speak a skill. And the the
language OF MASTERY, I'VE STUDIED it in
business, even in careers. It takes
between seven very early to 10 years to
be a MASTER OF SOMETHING. THAT'S WHY
SKILLS are key. When you know this is MY
PATH, I'M MEANT to be A DOCTOR. BEGIN TO
SHARPEN YOUR SKILLS IMMEDIATELY BETWEEN
7 TO 10 years. You ought to be a
consultant in that area.
The problem is
you are all over. Pick a path become the
best in it. Are we together? Are we
together? and and our curriculum was
very confusing because to my geography,
biology, English when you look at
yourself, you know something about
everything that is good for wisdom. But
now when you begin to enter into your
career path, if you do your degree in
economics, do your masters in economics,
do your PhD in economics, understand
that's how the west operates
in Kenya. You have a degree in teaching,
you have masters in accounts, and now
you are doing PhD in environment. Who
are you?
Tell your neighbor, neighbor
>> skills.
>> THE BIBLE SAYS HE WILL STAND BEFORE
KINGS. HE WILL NOT STAND BEFORE UNKNOWN
MEN WHEREVER YOU ARE. EVEN AS A PASTOR,
NEXT YEAR I'M GOING BACK TO SCHOOL. I'VE
made up my mind
BECAUSE THE WAY YOU GUYS ARE GROWING, I
CAN'T PREACH TO YOU IN THE NEXT 5 YEARS
AS I'm preaching TO YOU NOW. I MUST
SHARPEN MY SKILLS. I ASKED MY FRIEND I I
ASKED MY FRIEND AND I TOLD THE PERSON I
NEED TO GO TO a leadership school
BECAUSE THE WAY THE NUMBERS ARE GROWING
IN CHURCH THE NEXT CRISIS WILL NOT BE
ANOINTING IT will be management and
leadership and the person sent me links
of Harvard online. I said are you
serious? And the person told me IF YOU
ARE SERIOUS ABOUT SKILLS go to the best
schools.
Can I give something here?
I was told in the west
in the west
they have designed the system in a way
that only a very small percentage will
always break the ceiling of millionaires
and billionaires among the black
community. The system is so designed
that it has nothing to do with make
America great again is make America
white again
because of the superiority complex. And
because of that what they have done they
have made sure where our black people
live
they introduce mindsets and ideologies.
The biggest sound in the west is
hip-hop.
Hip hop is beyond a sound is a culture.
The biggest investors of hip hop is not
the black community is the white elites.
Because I was in New York and I was told
you know what that's Brooklyn that's a
black estate and there are areas there
that look like said what do you mean?
And they told me whatever you see on
hip-hop videos is what they amplify. So
what is that life? You buy expensive
watch, buy expensive cars, buy luxuries
at the expense of investment. When you
go to white community dominated centers,
they are building generational wealth.
When you go to the black community
centers, when a man dies, the family is
in poverty and now they must use the
channel of music. In fact, somebody said
whatever we are seeing them about PD PD,
I know you know you you I know you read.
I'm not here to defend the man. Whatever
he was doing, those parties are very
bad. But do you know there are worse
parties organized by the white community
worse than what he was organizing. But
because he's a black man who broke the
ceiling of billionaire, he must be
incriminated because by him breaking
that ceiling, he's an inspiration to
other black people.
That's why you in Kenya and that culture
has affected you. When you buy a car,
Somebody say skills.
>> SO YOU NEED TO SHARPEN your skills.
THIS IS THIS HAS NOTHING to do with
prayer. It has everything to do with
discipline. READ A BOOK. GO ONLINE,
STUDY SOMETHING. APPLY IT. DO IT AGAIN
AND AGAIN. Open your mind. INTERACT WITH
MEN THAT ARE OF THE SAME TRADE. LET
PEOPLE COME AND CHALLENGE YOU. GO AND
SEE WHAT OTHER PEOPLE ARE DOING.
SEE HOW THE FUN IS THERE ARE MAKING
THEIR BEDS LEARN BECAUSE WE ARE
PERPETUALLY LEARNING from men
AND SKILLS WILL GIVE YOU AN ADVANTAGE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY THESE MEN STAND BEFORE
NOBLE MEN? BECAUSE GREAT MEN CAN PAY ANY
PRICE FOR a skill.
WHEN YOU REACH AND BEGAN TO INTERACT
WITH THE RICH, THEY DON'T GAIN. IF YOU
CAN GIVE THEM WHAT THEY WANT, THEY WILL
GIVE YOU THE MONEY.
RICH MEN WILL ALWAYS TELL YOU, "GIVE me
a quote
um and let me let me know the account to
deposit." The moment they discover you
are skillful. Have you ever dealt with
rich people? Okay. Rich, rich
go in the process of being rich. But
there are those who have entered that
level and they don't but gain a lot. As
long as they get value for their money,
they will give you what you're LOOKING
FOR. THAT'S WHY SKILLFUL MEN AND ONE OF
THE THINGS to understand when you look
at that preacher, HE SAYS, DO YOU SEE A
MAN WHO EXCELS IN WORK? HE WILL STAND
BEFORE KINGS. THE OTHER PROBLEM HERE IS
WE HAVE SKILLFUL MEN THAT DON'T
UNDERSTAND the culture of royalty.
That's the other problem.
I I I HAD CALLED A FEW PEOPLE, WANTED TO
HAVE A MEETING. THE MAN TOLD ME I'M
COMING AT 12:00. THE FIRST MAN, HE TOLD
ME I'M COMING AT 12:00. At 11:45,
he texted me and said, "Sir, I'm around.
When you need me, let me know." I knew
this one is a serious man. And I knew
where he came from. We used to sing with
him.
One day was invited to get a contract in
the military. It was worth a lot of
money. They saw his CV. But when he
appeared on the gate, they told him
and he lost millions because he didn't
understand the culture of royalty.
mustache.
Now, now listen. I I just want to get
your attention because what I'm saying
is very important. Now, what we need to
understand, there is another culture
called the culture of royalty
because kings are not ordinary men. You
I we have many skillful men that don't
HAVE SOME SOME CHARACTER AND CHARISMA
AND PACKAGING TO ATTRACT KINGS. SO I
GIVE SOMEONE AN APPOINTMENT AND HE
DOESN'T TEXT ME. I CALL HIM AND HE TELLS
ME
and then where we are now supposed to
meet. And I said now you are the one
employing me. I'm not MEETING YOU THERE.
SOME OF US WE NEED THE CULTURE, WE NEED
THE GRAMMAR, WE NEED THE PACKAGING OF
PRESENTING ourselves before kings.
One of the books that helps us to
understand that is the book of Esther.
The protocols OF THE PALACE MUST BE
OBSERVED. IF TODAY YOU GOT ONE MINUTE OR
FIVE MINUTES TO TELL THE PRESIDENT OF
KENYA ABOUT YOUR BUSINESS, what will you
do? HOW IS YOUR GRAMMAR? HOW IS YOUR
PRESENTATION? WHICH NEED ARE YOU
SOLVING? What are you bringing on the
table?
SELFIE. SOMEONE SAID NEVER CONFUSE KYROS
moments for product moments. SOME
OPPORTUNITIES COME ONCE IN A LIFETIME.
THAT'S WHY SOMETIMES WHERE YOU GO FOR
INTERACTIONS MATTER. It cannot be every
day
STAGE HOTEL. THERE THERE ARE DEALS THAT
CAN NEVER BE CUT THERE. ONE day
people who sit on THOSE TABLES, YOU
CAN'T FIND THEM IN KANDU.
tell your neighbor neighbor
skills
will bring you before kings
and I feel like announcing here by faith
every life church member must have a
passport
>> yeah go and get one
>> now if today someone will someone if
someone sees your work on Facebook and
wants to fly you to South Africa and
then you begin to come here whatever
Be global ready.
>> Be global ready.
>> Are we together?
>> And the second thing I feel like saying
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE.
All of us are walking.
Nobody knows how you entered.
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR. YOU NEVER KNOW
WHO YOU'RE GOING TO MEET THERE. It's
called the principle of access.
Is someone listening to me?
>> Somebody say he will serve before kings.
He will not serve before obscure men.
Give me this in message Bible.
I'm about to finish. I'm happy I prayed
because now these are wisdoms.
Everybody read.
Everybody read. Observe
people who are good AT THEIR WORK.
SKILLED WORKERS ARE always
>> read it again.
>> May this be you.
>> They are admired. AND THEY ARE ALWAYS IN
DEMAND. BEYOND FAVOR, YOU NEED TO
perfect your skills.
The greatest buildup of what WE CALL
CLIENTELE IS NOT EVEN BY MARKETING, is
by referral.
ANYONE IN BUSINESS, THE greatest build
up of your clientele is by referral.
Pastor Ken Patrick has been making my
suits and there are times I tell people
who made and I say Ken Patrick and they
will not even ask anything. They go with
my trust. They say if you made a suit
for that man I need a suit like that.
It's called referral and how you handle
those who are referred to you because
you can handle a high client low level
referral. How you handle that referral
will matter whether you'll get another
business.
If every year you have new clients and
the old are leaving, you've not begun.
BUT IF YOU'VE RETAINED THE OLD AND
OTHERS ARE COMING, you are now growing.
That's how you know you're growing. SO,
SO THE SECOND THING THAT WE NEED TO grow
is stature. Somebody say stature.
>> Somebody say stature.
>> Stature is ability to release virtue. As
I begin to conclude, stature is ability
to release virtue. Stature is the
ability to release virtue. So capacity
capacity has everything to do with
skills
is a skillful enablerance that help you
solve matters. Stature is the ability to
release virtue
AND THERE ARE LEVELS WHEREBY YOUR
sustenance will not be a product of
skills. It will be a product of stature.
You cannot manage warfare by skills. YOU
CAN ONLY MANAGE WARFARE by stature.
THERE IS A REAL WHEREBY SKILLS CAN FAIL
AND it will take another dimension for
you to enter. Now look at Proverbs
18:16.
Proverbs 18:16.
Proverbs 18:16. Give me 2 minutes. My my
time is almost up, but give me 2
minutes. Proverbs 18:16. Everybody read.
Now we need to get this language very
clearly.
A skill is acquired but a gift is given.
You can have a skillful man that is
gifted
and every gifted man has skills but not
every skillful man is gifted.
Because we can all go to school and
acquire skills, but gifts come from the
Lord.
THE DIVINE ADVANTAGE of a believer is
not in skills only is when the believer
has the ability to operate from a skill
with an addition of a gift.
I used to tell people when I used to rap
I used to tell them I AM THE BEST RAPPER
not because of skills dynamics because
my competition don't have the gift I
have.
So there is a rapper who can sing and
flow but I am a gifted rapper because I
have the gift of the apostolic but I
have the skills of rapping. So my rap is
apostolic rap so you can't compete with
me.
Even if you bring the real OG, he knows
I'm the real original gospel. He knows
BECAUSE ONE IS OPERATING FROM SKILLS.
Another one is operating from gift. NOW
THE BIBLE SAYS A GIFT makes room.
WHERE THERE IS DOMINATION OF SKILLS. You
must have an advantage of gift to
survive.
THERE ARE MANY JOBLESS PEOPLE because
they are competing from a level of
skills. But when there is a gift, the
word there is mix. MEANING THAT THERE
WAS NO ROOM BUT THE GIFT will avail the
room.
NOW WHEN WE COME TO THE BAPTISMS OF THE
HOLY SPIRIT, WHAT THE HOLY SPIRIT GIVES
US IS gifts
is gifts. The gifts OF THE SPIRIT
MAJORITY OF THE TIME WHEN A MAN IS
operating from talent AND SKILL. TALENT
IS AN ABILITY OF natural birth. That's
talent. So you can have a talented
footballer who is also skillful but it
ends there. BUT A GIFT IS A IS A PRODUCT
of spiritual birth. SO WHEN YOU ARE A
NATURAL MAN YOU END AT SKILLS. You are
talented and skillful. WHEN YOU ARE A
MAN OF THE SPIRIT YOU CAN HAVE A TALENT
OUT OF NATURAL PATH. YOU CAN HAVE SKILLS
OUT OF accusation acquiring and you can
have a gift out of impartation.
I want to the weather is good. So I want
to go slowly. SO A NATURAL MAN. SO HERE
IS A HERE IS A BUSINESSMAN WHO IS A
TALENTED MARKETER AND HE HAS GONE AHEAD
TO STUDY SALES AS A SKILL BECAUSE SOME
OF YOU AS YOUNG AS CLASS TWO YOU ARE
SELLING SWEETS.
SO THERE WAS A BUSINESS DNA IN YOU. SO
YOU ARE A TALENTED MARKETER AND NOW YOU
NEED THE SKILLS OF SALES AND MARKETING.
SO YOU ARE NOW A PHD HOLDER OR A
GRADUATE OF SALES AND MARKETING AND THAT
IS ALL YOU CAN DO. BUT HERE IS A
talented marketer A SKILLFUL SALES and
marketing but a PROPHETIC MAN. SO BY THE
TIME PEOPLE ARE PREPARING THE GOODS HE
COME FROM THE ORDER OF ISSAKA. HE
UNDERSTANDS TIMES AND SEASONS. HE CAN
PREDICT THAT A CERTAIN GOOD WILL NOT DO
VERY WELL IN THE MARKET IN THIS SEASON.
THAT IS WHERE THE GIFT COMES IN AND
THAT'S WHERE OUR FAITH COMES IN.
WE ARE ALL IN THE SAME AREA. WE ARE
CALLED BUSINESSMEN. BUT ONE HAS AN
ADVANTAGE OF A GIFT. HE can discern
times and SEASON BY THE SYSTEM OF
PROPHETIC EYES. WHAT IS PROPHECY IS A
gift of the HOLY SPIRIT. SO WHEN THE MAN
IS PRAYING IN THE HOLY GHOST, HE'S NOT
PRAYING BECAUSE HE is an intercessor
only. HE'S PRAYING BECAUSE HE MUST
ACTIVATE THE GIFT BECAUSE the gift is an
advantage to his enterprise.
Hallelujah.
Now do you see where faith comes in? The
world will always end as skills, deals.
The church has an advantage of gift.
That's why in the gift of the spirit you
can carry the gift of discernment
that you are always in procurement or
you are you are doing what do we call um
you are doing um
supplies
AND SOMETHING BEGINS TO TELL YOU that
company is about to close down. There
are people who lost money when
supermarkets closed and they closed now
it's cold cases. There are people who
sell air. SOMEONE TOLD ME THERE ARE
PEOPLE WHEN they know you have a new
business they will open a warehouse and
tell you to supply goods and they will
give you an LPO and the moment you
supply after 14 days you find that they
are not there and there was no such a
business now you have been robbed BUT
SOMETHING CAN SUPPRESS YOUR APPETITE FOR
PROFIT AND DISCERNMENT JUST tells you
not THAT PERSON AND DISCERNMENT CAN BE
EXPRESSED THROUGH A DREAM and you
realize you 10 people stealing your
goods and you're like I don't know why
but let us not do business with this
person. It's an advantage when you're in
the marketplace.
Hallelujah. That's why you can hold a
deal before you enter a meeting. You
just tell the Lord, "Reveal to me who
THESE MEN ARE BEFORE I SIGN." BECAUSE
THE NAME SIGNATURE comes from the Greek
word seal. IT'S YOUR SPIRIT. BEFORE I
APPEND MY LIFE ON THIS CONTRACT, LORD,
REVEAL to me what is this job about.
THAT'S WHY NOW THE GIFTS OF THE SPIRIT
come in operation. I have word of
wisdom. I have word of knowledge. I have
discernment of spirits. I have I have
what do I call? I HAVE PROPHECY. SO WHEN
I SIT IN A MEETING, I know I have the
gift of faith. I'M A BUSINESSMAN. BUT
SOMETHING IS TELLING ME IT'S TIME TO
EXPAND 10 TIMES. IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE
ECONOMICALLY, BUT I have the gift of
faith.
Working out of miracles is beyond
healings. WHEN THE BIBLE SPEAKS ABOUT
healing is BEYOND DISEASES, A MARRIAGE
CAN BE HEALED. A BUSINESS CAN BE HEALED.
SOMEONE TOLD ME ANYTIME I DO BUSINESS
WITH SOMEONE THEIR BUSINESS MUST
SUCCEED. SO THAT'S WHY THE HOLY SPIRIT
GAVE MEN GIFTS. IS SOMEONE
UNDERSTANDING? YOU KNOW THE PROBLEM IS
THAT WE CONFINE THEM TO THE PULLPIT OF
SAYING DO I KNOW YOUR NAME? I USE SO AND
SO. IT IS OKAY. THAT'S ME WHEN I'M
OPERATING WITH A GIFT. BUT YOU too can
operate with a gift and it will begin to
make room for you.
YOU CAN IMAGINE IF YOU ARE A PROPHET IN
A COMPANY AND YOU'RE A MANAGER. YOU SIT
AMONG DIRECTORS AND TELL THEM THIS IS
NOTHING to do with the business but I
sense it's like if we enter into this
deal we'll lose money and THEY LOSE
MONEY THE NEXT time they'll listen to
you.
This how we become relevant not by
praying
and
somebody say gift.
>> We read three scriptures then we go
home. Exodus 36 from verse 1-2.
Exodus 36 from verse 1-2.
A gift is a product of spiritual
discipline. A gift is a product of
spiritual discipline. The Bible says and
Basel
and Aolab and every what gifted artisan
in whom the Lord has put wisdom and
understanding to know how to do all
manner of work for the service of the
sanctuary shall do according to all that
the Lord has commanded. Look at two
go to two the next one. Then Moses
called Bazale and Aholab and every
gifted artisan. A gift maketh room. A
gift will make great mind bow to you.
Genesis 41:37.
A gift will make generals, managers,
directors bow. Genesis 314 4137. 41:37.
WHATEVER
made Joseph to be relevant, it was not
skill, it was gift.
SO THE ADVICE WAS GOOD IN THE EYES OF
PHARAOH and in the eyes of all his
servant. Continue.
And Pharaoh said to HIS SERVANT, "CAN WE
FIND SUCH one as this? A man in whom is
the spirit of God? The spirit gives
gifts." 39 Then Pharaoh said to Joseph,
"In as much as God has shown you all
these things, THERE IS NO ONE AS
DISCERNING. DISERNMENT IS A GIFT. AND AS
WISE AS YOU.
You shall be, everybody read, you shall
be over my house AND ALL MY PEOPLE SHALL
BE RULED ACCORDING to
>> only IN REGARD TO THE THRONE WILL I be
greater than you. That is to tell you
Pharaoh became a caretaker king.
THE MAN RULING EGYPT WAS JOSEPH. WHAT
GAVE JOSEPH AN AN ADVANTAGE? The gift of
interpreting dreams. That was not a
skill. IT WAS A GIFT.
THAT IS WHAT CREATED A PRIME MINISTER
POST. IT WAS NOT THERE. IT WAS NOT
THERE.
IN THAT GOVERNMENT, THE CONSTITUTION DID
NOT THINK of a prime minister, BUT THEY
HAD TO THINK OF A POWERFUL PRIME
MINISTER WHERE THE PRESIDENT IS A
CELEBRATED PRESIDENT. And this pattern
is what works in Israel today. Israel
has a president, but we know the prime
MINISTER BECAUSE A MAN CAME OUT OF A
GIFT AND delivered a nation. Let us look
at THE FINAL SCRIPTURE. DANIEL CHAPTER
number two from verse 46 to 48. Daniel
chapter number 2 from 46- 48. I'm
believing God we are going to raise
talented, skillful, gifted. That shall
be your pattern.
>> You are a talented, SKILLFUL, GIFT,
GIFTED marketplace man.
WHEREVER YOU ENTER, YOU SHALL BECOME AN
ADVANTAGE to that company. ANY BUSINESS
YOU ARE DOING, IT SHALL BECOME AN
ADVANTAGE TO the economy.
Then Nebuchadnezzar fell on his face
portrait. Everybody read. Then King
NEBUCHADNEZZAR FELL ON HIS FACE PORTRAIT
BEFORE DANIEL AND COMMANDED that they
should present an offering an incense to
him. Look at 47.
THE KING ANSWERED AND SAID, "TRULY, your
God is the God of gods, the Lord of
kings, and a revealer of secret. Since
you could reveal this secret, what was
the secret? the dream of the king. 48
Then the king promoted Daniel and gave
him many great gifts and he made him
ruler over the whole province of
Babylon. Everybody read this is the
level of promotion. I know the Bible
says promotion does not come from the
north either the south but allow me to
tell you promotion is pegged on a gift.
This promotion was not scheduled but
BECAUSE OF A MAN'S gift this thing began
to happen.
I remember Brian here told me
he sat in one of the very complicated
boardrooms.
Blessed memory Chris Kubi looked at him
one day and told him you are sitting
here because we know you pray. So it is
your gift that has given you access not
skills.
Hi. Then the king promoted Daniel.
21 days of promotion.
Every devil in my father's house scatter
many great gifts. and he made him ruler
over the whole province of Babylon and
chief administrator.
These men are now entrusted with money
over all. So he was made the leader of
the witches.
These wise men were witches
of Babylon.
Genesis 27:40.
Then we make a prayer.
Genesis
27:40.
The Bible says, "By your sword you shall
live and shall serve your brother. And
it shall come to pass when you become
restless that you shall break his yoke
from your neck." This is the word the
Lord gave me for people who are here.
The day you become restless,
you will begin to do some things.
As long as you are not restless, you
will be okay to operate with some yolks
of operation.
And this I remember one day prophet
Monki told me.
You enter your room and say I vow with a
vow sleep. You are my enemy. One man
told me the two greatest enemies of
humanity is food and sleep. Dr. Paul
said whoever conquers those two enemies
has destiny.
Food
and sleep.
BY YOUR SWORD YOU shall live and you
shall serve your brother. This is the
blessing of Jacob to Esau. AND IT SHALL
COME TO pass when may this day be the
day of your when when you become
restless.
Somebody must rise and look themselves
from the mirror fresh and say by the way
I know who I am. It is time to rise and
begin to work on what God has called me
to do. when you become restless that you
shall break his yoke from your neck.
One of the daughters in the house,
Grace, were in the hospital and she was
giving me a story. She told me there's a
time a man died in the hospital and she
felt in her spirit, no, this man must
say bye-bye to her to his people. And
all the doctors tried to jump start the
man. He couldn't come back. Just went
and laid hands and said, in the name of
Jesus, you wake up and say bye to your
people. And the man came back. Now that
is not skill of medicine because they
did that thing. It never worked. It is
called a gift of the spirit. So the
doctors asking, "What did you do?" And
she's like, "Uh, there's another jump
starter.
By the laying on of hands, something
began to work. The church is not
disadvantaged. May you locate your gift.
You can be an apostle in the
marketplace." What does that mean? You
carry the gift of territory. That where
you set a business, you control prices.
Hey, that people look at what you are
doing for them to do what they need to
do. That's apostolic. Cuz a one of the
anointings of the apostles is called a
proton anointing. It is a beginners.
It is territorial. YOU CAN BE A PROPHET
IN the marketplace that you are able to
see things that have not yet come to
pass. I know a friend, we used to SING
WITH HIM. HE WAS A DJ BUT A PROPHET. And
he was one of the wealthiest business
people in music. I EVEN MET HIM THE
OTHER DAY. I SHOOK HIS HAND. I told him,
"I know you are a prophet." And he told
me, "I have a solution for Kenya. I want
to meet the president. I know how we can
employ 1 million youth through fintech."
and what he sees is always 5 years
ahead. So when I listen it didn't make
sense. A FRIEND OF MINE WE ARE WORKING
WITH HIM AND THEN HE TELLS ME Buddha
windmill
DISRUPTION BUT A MAN HAS EYES TO KNOW
THE NEXT PHASE OF ENERGY IS CLEAN
ENERGY. BEFORE THE CONVERSATION OF
ENVIRONMENTAL ENERGY THE MAN HAD SEEN IN
THE SPIRIT THE CONVERSATION OF THE
GLOBE. We we WE ARE NOT JUST MEN
CARRIERS OF BIBLES AND OIL. WE ARE
CARRIERS OF THE GIFTS OF THE FATHER SO
THAT THERE CAN BE SOLUTIONS IN OUR LIFE.
LIFT UP YOUR HAND AND SAY LORD LOCATE ME
TO MY GIFT NOW. WHATEVER GIFT THAT
CONNECTS WITH MY ASSIGNMENT, LET IT
LOCATE ME NOW IN THE NAME OF JESUS. I
RECEIVE THE GRACE TO BE RESTLESS
UNTIL I BREAK THE YOKE THAT HAS KEPT ME
WHERE I AM. JUST MAKE THAT PRAY IN ONE
MINUTE WHILE YOU ARE SEATED. MAKE IT A
PERSONAL PRAYER. RECEIVE THE GRACE.
RECEIVE THE GRACE NOW. RECEIVE THE
ANOINTING. SOME OF YOU, YOU MUST SAY
BYE-BYE TO SLUMBER. YOU MUST SAY BYE-BYE
TO SOME THINGS. SOME OF YOU, BY THE TIME
WE ARE COMING TO JANUARY, YOU MUST
ENROLL BACK TO SCHOOL, GET ANOTHER
SKILL. YOU HAVE BEEN PROCRASTINATING FOR
LONG. THE TIME IS NOW. THE DEPOSITS OF
HEAVEN ARE UPON YOU. LET THE SPIRIT OF
PRAYER BE UPON YOU TO BEGIN TO ACTIVATE
THE THE GIFTS OF GOD. SOME OF YOU, YOU
ARE ANOINTED BUT YOU DON'T KNOW. YOU
DON'T KNOW THE ANOINTING UPON YOUR LIFE.
IT IS BEYOND PULLPIT ASSIGNMENT. THEY
ARE GRACES UPON OUR LIVES BECAUSE OF
WHERE WE ARE. EVEN IN THE MARKETPLACE,
WE SHALL SEE APOSTLES. WE shall see pro
prophets. WE SHALL SEE EVANGELISTS. WE
SHALL SEE TEACHERS. WE SHALL SEE MEN
OPERATING IN THE GIFTS OF THE SPIRIT,
THE GIFTS OF THE FATHER. RISING IS A
COMBINATION OF GIFT, skills and talent.
And now I declare over your life in the
name of Jesus,
the potential in you will not be cut
short.
You will manifest everything that is in
you. Some of you next year as early as
now, November, December, you need to be
looking for the school to enroll into.
You need another skill.
You cannot be street smart the whole of
your life. One day, boardroom smart will
deplete street smart. You must be street
smart and boardroom smart. Boardrooms
are controlled by skills.
The streets are controlled by talents.
For you to have a share, you must have
skills, talents, and gifts. Hallelujah.
I release you to the place of your grace
where God has planted you by this
revelation. Go and manifest. Go and
conquer. go and become a master
of something in Jesus name. In Jesus
name.